Contact

7184047920 (Mobile) j.dominguez6045@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jeffdominguez-bsn-rn-ccrnk-93b4b25a (LinkedIn) www.conciergetaxconsultants.com (Company)

Top Skills

Healthcare
Data Analysis
Statistics

Languages

German (Professional Working)
Italian (Limited Working)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Zertifikat Deutsch CCRN Pediatric Program H/C PRI

Honors-Awards

Thomas Jefferson University School of Nursing Scholarship

Thomas Jefferson University School of Nursing Scholarship

Helen Auerbach Hodes Award National Association of Hispanic Nurses 40 under 40 Ángeles Del 41

Jeff Dominguez BSN, RN, CCRN-K

Nurse Care Manager - Solid Organ Transplant at NewYork-Presbyterian Hospital

New York, New York

Summary

Jeff is a capable, articulate Nurse Care Manager with strong executive presence. He is highly engaged in the Care Coordination department, hospital and the greater professional community; including holding the role of President of the NY Chapter of the National Association of Hispanic Nurses and attending American Case Management Association leadership programming. Jeff is active on the Nurse Care Coordination/ Social Work QA Committee and represents the Care Coordination department as a subject matter expert for the EPIC build and the QVENTUS artificial intelligence initiative at NewYork Presbyterian-Columbia. Jeff is able to tailor his communication to the needs of his audience to ensure care is delivered in a timely and appropriate manner. His commitment to grassroots-driven systemic change is refreshing and empowers his colleagues. He approaches new experiences with curiosity and persistence; ensuring that he secures comprehensive high quality care and rare resources for his patients. He is widely known as a skilled communicator and is recognized as a trusted professional nurse by his patients, colleagues and leaders. He is often called upon to represent the Care Coordination department in institution-wide and community settings. Jeff models collaboration across teams and disciplines.

He manages the care of patients from 3 different transplant teams, Lung, Liver and Renal and other surgical service lines. He has to tailor his communication style to the providers he is working with to facilitate timely and appropriate care. He is respectful and collaborative in all of these interactions and always re-centers the discussion on patient care and improving outcomes.

Jeff is able to build immediate rapport with colleagues, even in tense situations. He is an emotionally intelligent professional registered nurse who reads interpersonal dynamics to adjust his communication style appropriately.

Experience

Concierge Tax Consultants

Nurse Entrepreneur

January 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months)

New York, NY

We prepare individual tax returns with accuracy and efficiency. We have a wide knowledge base with respect to tax returns for health care professionals. Join the many Nurses, Paramedics, Physicians, PAs, CNAs, EMTs and other professionals that benefit from our services. Learn more from us by navigating our site. We are committed to providing personalized attention and support. We look forward to helping you optimize your tax savings.

New York-Presbyterian Hospital 5 years 6 months

Nurse Care Manager-Solid Organ Transplant November 2016 - Present (3 years 7 months) Greater New York City Area

Coordinate all aspects of the care for Lung, Liver and Renal transplant patients. Focus on financial management and resource utilization to yield both improved patient and cost-effective outcomes.

Certified CCRN in the Pediatric Cardiac ICU December 2014 - November 2016 (2 years) Morgan Stanley Children's Hospital of New York

Bedside clinician for pediatric patients undergoing Cardio-Thoracic surgery for congenital heart defect repairs and Heart Transplants. Proficient in ECMO circuit, open chest, central lines, High frequency oscillatory ventilation (HFOV), Jet ventilation, mechanical ventilation and Continuous Veno-Venous Hemofiltration (CVVH). Proficient in management of patients on left ventricular assist device (LVAD) including the Berlin Heart, Toyobo and Heartmate 2 and 3.

National Association of Hispanic Nurses - New York Chapter President Of The Board Of Directors January 2019 - December 2019 (1 year) New York, New York

Served on the Board for 3 years total

The Children's Hospital of Philadelphia

Page 2 of 3

1 year 6 months

Registered Nurse July 2014 - October 2014 (4 months)

CCU/CPRU Nurse Tech August 2013 - July 2014 (1 year) Philadelphia, PA

CICU Nurse Extern May 2013 - August 2013 (4 months) Philadelphia, PA

Lenox Hill Hospital
Emergency Medical Technician
June 2005 - February 2012 (6 years 9 months)
New York City

Respond to 911 medical emergencies and provide basic life support.

Education

Columbia University School of Nursing
MS Advanced Clinical Management and Leadership, Health Care
Administration/Management/Leadership · (2018 - 2021)

Thomas Jefferson University

B.S.N, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2014)

Hunter College
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), German Studies · (2001 - 2006)